[
  {
    "Question": "Anwaarul Haq Kakar was sworn in as the _______ interim prime minister of Pakistan on 14th August 2023?",
    "option1": "8th",
    "option2": "9th",
    "option3": "7th",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 4,
    "Category": "navy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is the current caretaker Prime minister of Pakistan?",
    "option1": "Ishaq dar",
    "option2": "Jalil Abbas jilani",
    "option3": "Anwaarul Haq Kakar",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 4,
    "Category": "navy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was the Caretaker Prime Minister of Pakistan in 2018?",
    "option1": "Justice (retd) Nasirul Mulk",
    "option2": "Maleeha lodhi",
    "option3": "former chief justice Tassaduq Hussain Jilani",
    "option4": "None of them",
    "CorrectOption": 1,
    "Category": "army"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was the 1st Caretaker Prime Minister of Pakistan?",
    "option1": "Balakh Sher Mazari",
    "option2": "Moeenuddin Ahmad Qureshi",
    "option3": "Mir Hazar Khan Khoso",
    "option4": "Ghulam Mustafa Jatoi",
    "CorrectOption": 4,
    "Category": "army"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who has become the second person from Balochistan province to be the interim prime minister of Pakistan?",
    "option1": "Main Muhammad Soomro",
    "option2": "Anwar ul Haq Kakar",
    "option3": "Sadiq Sanjrani",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 2,
    "Category": "airforce"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pakistan celebrates __________ years of independence on 14 August 2023?",
    "option1": "74 years",
    "option2": "76 years",
    "option3": "75 years",
    "option4": "77 years",
    "CorrectOption": 2,
    "Category": "airforce"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who signed the summary to dissolve the Provincial Assembly of Balochistan on 12th August 2023?",
    "option1": "President Arif Alvi",
    "option2": "Justice Naeem Akhtar Afghan",
    "option3": "Governor Malik Abdul Wali Khan Kakar",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "CorrectOption": 3,
    "Category": "airforce"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Under which article Governor Wali Kakar approved the dissolution of the provincial assembly of Balochistan?",
    "option1": "Article 116(1)",
    "option2": "Article 115(1)",
    "option3": "Article 112(1)",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 4,
    "Category": "navy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which provincial assembly has been dissolved on 12th August 2023?",
    "option1": "Sindh",
    "option2": "Khyber Pakhtunkhwa",
    "option3": "Balochistan",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 3,
    "Category": "army"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Provincial Assembly of Balochistan has been dissolved on ____________?",
    "option1": "August 12th 2023",
    "option2": "August 10th 2023",
    "option3": "August 8th 2023",
    "option4": "None of These",
    "CorrectOption": 2,
    "Category": "airforce"
  }
]
